gofynd.com 2019-08-05

# Privacy Policy : Fynd Care

********

## Privacy Policy 

Modified on: Mon, 11 Dec, 2017 at 4:11 PM

* * *

### INTRODUCTION

We are Shopsense Retail Technologies Private Limited, hereinafter referred to as Fynd. When you use Fynd services, you trust us with your information. This Privacy Policy will help you make informed decisions about your relationship with us. Please take a moment to read through it and let us know if you have any questions.

This Privacy Policy will aim to explain what data gets collected, why we collect certain others by permission, and finally what we do and don't do with it. You'll also find out that you are specifically able to control the shared information and manage your privacy and security while you safely and comfortably shop online with Fynd.

When you agree to our Privacy Policy, you give us the right to collect information and use it for the purposes described in the following sections.

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE GATHER?

All the information we collect is related to providing the Fynd service and its features. Some of this collected information is necessary for you to shop on Fynd and some information is required for us to provide better services to you - e.g knowing your current location to show you brands around you, information that can help us understand your fashion taste to show you collections or deals you'll find most interesting. We also try to understand the best time to provide you with hyperlocal service, gauge relevance to your content preferences or personalized fashion recommendations based on your demographic, purchase history, current location, seasonal occasions and time of the day.

Let us explore these points in detail.

Personal information you share with us: When you sign up to use Fynd, we securely receive and store the information you enter. This could be your full name, email address, password, mobile number, gender and payment details. You will be able to use Fynd even if you opt out of sharing certain personal information but then you may lose out on some of our advanced features. We never show or disclose your payment information to any third-party without your consent, apart from the payment gateway and the bank, and this data management shall always be Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI DSS) guideline compliant, updated and according to latest industry standards.

If you connect to Fynd using credentials from a Third Party Application (as defined in the Terms of service) (e.g., Facebook), you authorise us to collect your authentication information, such as your username and encrypted access credentials. We may also collect other information available on or through your third-party application account, including, for example, your name, profile picture, country, hometown, email address, date of birth, gender, friends' names, profile pictures, and networks.

We will never scan or import your contacts unless you explicitly allow us to. If you choose to do so, we will only use your contact information to help you find friends or contacts who also use Fynd.

We will be clear with you about how and when we might share information.

Automatic information: In addition to the personal information you share with us, we receive and store certain types of information when you use Fynd. Like many common websites or mobile applications, we obtain certain types of information when you interact with our services or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Fynd on other third-party services. This information often includes,

Device-specific information such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number.

Historical details of how you used our service, such as your search queries. This enable us to make suggestions based on your general location, like brands around you or relevant promotions.

Broad, non-specific location, which we derive from your IP address.

Device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.

Cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your Fynd account.

Location information: For us to show you lifestyle products around you, we collect and process information about your current location. We use technologies like IP address, Wi-Fi, GPS, beacons and other sensors for this purpose. This may also, for example, provide Fynd with information on connected devices, Wi-Fi access points and nearby cell towers.

Unique application numbers: Our service includes a unique application number. This number and information about your installation (for example, the operating system type and application version number) may be sent to our servers when you install or uninstall the Fynd app or when it periodically contacts our servers, for automatic updates.

Local storage: To serve you relevant content when you use Fynd, we may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.

Cookies and similar technologies: We and our partners may use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit our service, and this may include using cookies or similar technologies to identify your browser or device. We may also use such technologies to receive, store and share information when you use Fynd with our partners, such as advertising services, third-party applications or Fynd features that may appear on other sites.

E-mail, SMS and In-App communications: We love to proactively reach out to our users to inform you about service updates, new collections/brands and other such relevant information related to the Fynd service. To help us make these e-mails/SMS/In-App communications (push notifications or interstitials) more useful and interesting, we often receive and analyse information on how you interact with these communications. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers.

Information from other sources: We may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

In the Profile/My Account section, we indicate the controls and relevant settings associated with your Fynd account.

### WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

When you agree to the terms set in this policy you give us permission to collect information that includes your personal information. Consistent with the policy, the information we collect helps us serve you:

1\. with personalised recommendations, curated fashion collections, promotions and customer service

2\. help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts, correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services

3\. develop new products and services pertaining to Fynd, analyse your use of the service, including your interactions with the application, advertising, products and services that are made available, linked to, or offered through Fynd

4\. to communicate with you for service related or technical updates via emails, notifications, text or other messages which you agree to receive

5\. to communicate with you directly, or through our partners, for marketing and promotional purposes via emails, notifications, or other messages, consistent with any permissions you may have communicated to us

6\. with securely processing your payments, maintaining your bag, wishlists, promotions or offers from your account, and prevent any associated fraud or abuse on the service

7\. with features, information, advertising, or other content which is influenced by your location

8\. enforce this Privacy Policy, the Terms of service, and any other terms that you have agreed to, including to protect the rights, property, or safety of Fynd, its users, or any other person, or the copyright protected content of the service

We may use your public information to promote the service, including through Facebook and other Third Party Applications and websites that externally links to the Fynd service. Your information may be used to notify others, including within the service, via email, and through Facebook and third-party applications, about your use of the service (e.g., that you have joined Fynd or activity related to a Fynd bag, such as purchases.)

### CONSENT

How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to login, complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

How do I withdraw my consent?

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at care@gofynd.com or mailing us at: Fynd, A 317, Sagar Tech Plaza, Saki Naka, Andheri East, Mumbai, MH, 400072, India

### DISCLOSURE

By agreeing to this policy you give us the right to disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, certain third-party rights owners, or others in the good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

1\. enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy

2\. respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third-party

3\. or protect the rights, property, civil or personal safety of our users or the general public

### INFORMATION SECURITY

We are committed to protecting our users' information. All user accounts are password protected. We recommend you use a unique password and exercise general password discipline to safeguard your account and related details.

While we take industry compliant data protection precautions, no security measures are completely secure, and we do not guarantee the security of user information. We have stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Critical information on our backend is SSL encrypted. We adhere to strict security guidelines when we handle your information, protecting it against unauthorised access.

We give restricted access to Fynd employees, contractors and agents who need to know the information in order to process it, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may even be terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

### PAYMENT INFORMATION

If you sign up on the Fynd service (as defined in the Terms of Service) and/or purchase item/s (as defined in the Terms of Service), through Fynd, your credit or debit card information (such as card type and expiration date) and other financial data that we need to process your payment may be collected and stored by us and/or the payment processors with which we work. We may also collect some limited information, such as your postal code and delivery address, mobile number, and details of your transaction history, all of which are necessary to provide the service. In addition, the payment processors generally provide us with some limited information related to you, such as a unique token that enables you to make additional purchases using the information they've stored, and your card type, expiration date, and certain digits of your card number.

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then our partner Payment Gateway stores your Credit Card/Debit Card data which is encrypted in compliance with industry standard Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only for the duration of your purchase transaction.

### THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

Please remember that certain information is always publicly available, which means that it can be accessed by third-party applications through our APIs and developer tools. Based on your permissions, some additional information can be shared with third party applications and with others through third party applications. For example, you can use your settings to controls notifications you receive from Fynd. Similarly, you may consent to provide third party applications with access to your email address, subscription status, location, birthday, or similar information, upon their request.

For example, we work with service providers to host our Customer Delights applications and analytics providers to help us understand the use of our services. Where a third-party processes user data on our behalf (e.g. a hosting service provider), it is subject to security and confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy and applicable law. Where a third-party processes user data on its own behalf, such as a Payment Gateway, its processing is subject to its own Privacy Policy and applicable law.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Sri Lanka and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in India, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under Indian legislation.

### External Links

We may display advertisements from third-parties and other content that links to third-party websites. We cannot control or be held responsible for third-parties' privacy practices and content. Please read their privacy policies to find out how they collect and process your personal information.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Occasionally we may, in our discretion, make changes to this policy. When we make significant changes, we'll provide you with prominent notice as appropriate under the circumstances, e.g. by displaying a prominent notice within the service or by sending you an email. In some cases, we will notify you in advance, and your continued use of the service after the changes have been made will constitute your acceptance of the changes. Please make sure you read any such notice carefully.

If our services are acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to provide the same service to you.

If you do not wish to continue using the service under the new version of the policy, you may terminate your use of the service as outlined in the previous section, under 'How do I withdraw my consent?'.

If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, then please do not use the service.

By agreeing to sign up for Fynd after reading this policy, as may be amended from time to time by Fynd in its discretion, you also agree and consent to us collecting, storing, processing, transferring and sharing information (that includes sensitive personal information) related to you and/or with third-parties or service providers for the purposes as set out in this policy.

### QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information, contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at care@gofynd.com or by mail at

Fynd

501, 5th Floor, Corporate Centre, Andheri (E), Mumbai - 400 059

* * *

Did you find it helpful? Yes No

Send feedback

Sorry we couldn't be helpful. Help us improve this article with your feedback.
